<!-- This is used to install the plugin as an add-on: https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/18.1/ug-editor/topics/packing-and-deploying-addons.html#packing-and-deploying-addons -->
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
	<xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
		id="com.oxygenxml.cmis">
		<xt:location href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-cmis-plugin/releases/download/v1-sa/oxygen-cmis-workspace-access-1.0-SNAPSHOT-plugin.zip" />
		<xt:version>1.0.0</xt:version> 
		<xt:oxy_version>18.1+</xt:oxy_version>
		<xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
		<xt:author>Syncro Soft</xt:author>
		<xt:name>Oxygen CMIS plugin</xt:name>
		<xt:description>
			<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
				<head>
					<title>Oxygen CMIS plugin</title>
					<style type="text/css">
						ol {margin-top:0px;}
						p {margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:5px;}
					</style>
				</head>
				<body>
					<div>
						<h1>About the plugin</h1>
						<p>The plugin enables users to browse and edit resources from CMIS-enabled servers, like <a href="https://docs.alfresco.com/4.0/concepts/content-server-about.html">Alfresco</a>
							or <a href="https://www.ibm.com/support/knowledgecenter/en/SSNW2F_5.2.0/com.ibm.installingp8cmis.doc/cmidv000.htm">IBM FileNet</a>. It contributes a new view, named <b>CMIS Explorer</b>. If the <b>CMIS
								Explorer</b> view is not visible, you can open it from the <b>Window > Show
									View</b> menu.</p>
						<div>
							
							<h1>Connecting to a CMIS server</h1>
							<p>The plugin supports the  Atom Publishing Protocol binding. The structure of such
								an URL depends on the server. </p>
							<div>
								<h2>Alfresco content application server</h2>
								<p>http://localhost:8088/alfresco/api/-default-/cmis/versions/1.1/atom</p>
							</div>
							
							
							<div>
								<h2>IBM FileNet content application server</h2>
								<p>When IBM CMIS is properly configured and deployed, you can access the index
									page at http://host_name:port/context_root/index.jsp. By default, the
									context root of IBM CMIS for FileNet Content Manager is <samp
										class="ph codeph">fncmis</samp>. On the index page you will see the
									RESTful AtomPub binding. More details: <a
										href="https://www.ibm.com/support/knowledgecenter/en/SSNW2F_5.2.0/com.ibm.installingp8cmis.doc/cmidv009.htm"
										>IBM CMIS for FileNet Content Manager index page</a></p>
							</div>
						</div>
						
						<div>
							<h2>Connecting to a repository</h2>
							<p>Once you've discovered your RESTful AtomPub binding you just have to paste the URL
								inside the <b>Server URL</b> combo box and click <b>Connect</b>. If there are
								multiple repositories available, you can change between them from the
								<b>Repository</b> combo box.</p>
							<p><img src="img/connect.png" alt="Connecting to server"/></p></div>
						
						<div>
							<h2>Browsing the resources</h2>
							<p>In the view you can browse through resources by double clicking on folders. As
								you navigate, you can use the <b>Breadcrumb</b> view to return to a previous
								location.</p>
							<p><img src="img/browse.png" alt="Browsing resources" /></p>
						</div>
						
						<div>
							<h2>Working with documents</h2>
							<p>To open a document <b>for inspection</b> you can just double click it or select
								<b>Open document</b> from the contextual menu . Please note that the
								document will be opened in <b>Read-Only</b> mode. If you want to edit the
								document you'll have to first choose <b>Check out</b> and after that <b>Open
									document</b></p>
							<p><img src="img/contextualMenu.jpg" alt="Resource contextual menu." /></p>
							<p>Once you've checked-out a document, nobody else will be able to perform a
								check-out and edit it. You will be the only person that can change that
								document. After you've finished working on a document, you can commit it using
								the <b>Check in</b> action.</p>
							<p><img src="img/checkIn.png" alt="Document Check in" /></p>
							<p>A dialog will appear in which you can give a commit message and choose if this
								will be a minor version or a major version:</p>
							<p><img src="img/commit.png" alt="Commit message dialog" /></p>
							<p>You can also <b>Rename</b>, <b>Delete</b> or <b>Copy</b> a document by using the
								coresponding actions from the contextual menu.</p>
						</div>
						
						<div>
							<h2>Creating new documents</h2>
							<div>
								<p>When you create a new document, you have the possibility to save it directly to the Server:</p>
								<p><img src="img/create_new_doc_1.png" alt="Create a new document"/></p>
								<ol>
									<li><p>Invoke the <b>New...</b> action on the toolbar. </p></li>
									<li><p>Select the <b>Save As</b> check box.</p></li>
									<li>Browse for a folder on the CMIS server.</li>
									<li>Set a proper file name.</li>
								</ol>
							</div>
							
							<div>
								<p>In case if you've create a document without saving it to the server or is it's a local file, you need to do the following:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>
										Go to the File menu > Save to URL and choose "Browse CMIS" in the dialog that pops up.
									</li>
									<li>A dialog will appear in which you can browse for a folder on the server. Select a folder and press OK.</li>
								</ul>
								
								<div>
									<h2>Searching for documents</h2>
									<p>There is a search field in the top part of the view in which you type words to
										search. Press <b>Enter</b> and the results will be presented.</p>
									<p><img src="img/search.png" alt="Search for documents" /></p>
								</div>
							</div>
						</div>
						
						
						
					</div>            
					
				</body>
			</html>
			
		</xt:description>
		<xt:license><![CDATA[
			Copyright 2018 Syncro Soft SRL
			
			Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
			you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
			You may obtain a copy of the License at
			
			http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
			
			Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
			distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
			WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
			See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
			limitations under the License.
			
			This plugin may include certain of the following third party software components.
			The license terms applicable to such third party software components are listed below:
			
			
			
			
			
			]]></xt:license>
	</xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>


